(Penny:)Okay, I'm done.
(Penny:)- How did you guys finish so fast?
- I don't know, there were a lot of pictures.
(Bernadette:)And one page only had the word
"brakka-dooom!"
(Penny:)Yeah, well, I have street smarts.
(Bernadette:)So, what'd you guys think?
- Well, there was a lot of action.
- Hmm.
(Amy:)And the story moved along
at a brisk pace.
(Amy:)It was, overall,
what's the word I'm looking for?
- Stupid?
- So stupid.
(Penny:)I don't know how Leonard
can get so caught up.
(Bernadette:)It's crazy. They spend hours arguing
about things that don't even exist.
- What a waste of time.
- I know.
(Penny:)A hammer so heavy
that no one else can pick it up?
I don't think it's heavy, I think it's some
sort of magic so only Thor can lift it.
(Penny:)That makes even less sense, I mean...
(Amy:)No, no, no, it doesn't.
(Amy:)Thor is a god. The hammer is his.
Only he can use it.